[microphone feedback]
[♪ opening theme music playing]
FLEX X COP 2
CHARACTERS, PLACES, ORGANIZATIONS,
AND EVENTS IN THIS DRAMA ARE FICTITIOUS
ALL CHILD ACTORS FILMED
IN A SAFE ENVIRONMENT
[exhales deeply]
[Changun] Joo.
[in English] Would you like
something to drink?
[in Korean] You did a great job.
You too, sir.
Working with you again
felt like old times.
-[chuckles softly]
-I could really count on you.
Me too.
What did you think of Jin Isoo?
[inhales deeply]
He can be a bit odd,
and he's unpredictable,
but he's got good instincts.
And he's quite serious about the job.
Right?
He's actually a decent detective.
Do you have someone lined up
to lead Team 1?
[inhales deeply]
No. [exhales]
No one.
So I was wondering...
Someone just like you
would be perfect for the job.
Someone who's capable,
can manage Detective Jin,
and has real charisma.
Someone of that caliber
is really hard to come by.
[chuckles]
[Isoo] Hello!
[crowd cheering]
[cheers]
When did you have time to make these?
Hi there! Want a photo?
[Junyoung sighs]
He's going overboard again.
[Kyungjin] Come on, it's all good fun.
Okay, band.
Let's give it a try.
Just like we practiced. Ready!
[shouts command]
[♪ triumphant brass fanfare playing]
-[in English] Stop!
-[Taegyun, in Korean] What in the world...
What is all this?
Sir!
Oh, for heaven's sake.
-That good for nothing...
-Sir.
Come on, clear all this out.
[exclaims scornfully]
-This was Jin Isoo's doing.
-Sir!
[Isoo] It's for my new boss.
You know the drill.
Let's do this.
Somebody's working hard.
Of course.
We're getting a new team leader.
Oh. Incoming!
[♪ triumphant brass fanfare playing]
[engine shuts off]
[music stops]
[♪ upbeat rock music playing]
Joo Hyera?
I didn't expect such a grand welcome.
[chuckles softly]
Detective Jin has been busy
since this morning.
I guess you can be sweet.
This is the new team leader of Violent
Crime Investigation Team 1, Joo Hyera.
She's got years on you boys.
She was on our Violent Crime Team
before moving to Counterterrorism.
[chuckles softly]
Detective Jin, take good care
of your new boss.
Take good care of her.
Detective Jin Isoo,
Detective Park Junyoung,
Detective Choi Kyungjin.
Glad to join the team.
[muttering] This has to be a nightmare.
It's real.
Get used to it.
Looking forward to it, nutjob.
But why?
She has it good
in Counterterrorism, so why, huh?
That's true.
Why the sudden transfer?
[sighs] I'm seriously doomed.
What are you talking about?
She's a capable,
experienced veteran detective.
We don't get along.
She doesn't like me.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Nutjob. Hey, nutjob.
Hey, nutjob!
[tires screeching]
Hey, nutjob.
[Junyoung] It's nothing new.
I didn't like you at first, either.
[chuckling]
Sir!
What?
So...
About Detective Joo Hyera.
I heard she worked here before.
Yeah.
We worked together for about a year or so.
Then why did she come back here?
Beats me.
Ah.
It must be to torment you.
[exclaims] Come on, be serious!
She's good at her job.
She's pretty laid-back, so don't worry.
[♪ quirky music playing]
How old is she?
[inhales sharply]
Same age as you, I think.
-Same age as me?
-Yes.
By the way, don't ever make bets with her.
-Why not?
-She's kind of competitive...
No, she's insanely competitive.
She always has to win.
Hmm...
[mouse clicks]
-[game mine explodes]
-[sighs]
-[knock at door]
-Yes, come in.
Oh, Detective Joo Hyera.
Come in and have a seat.
[Taegyun exhales]
I appreciate you
taking on this tough role.
[chuckles softly] Not at all.
You also successfully closed
the bombing case.
We're lucky to have you.
You're too kind.
By the way,
I have one favor to ask of you.
Of course. Please, go ahead.
It's about Jin Isoo.
[sighs]
I can't sleep at night because of him.
Strictly speaking,
those bombings wouldn't have happened
if it weren't for him.
What's a spoiled rich kid doing
running wild in the police force?
God knows what he did, but he won over
everyone in Violent Crime and Chief Park.
Discipline's gone to hell around here.
Discipline's important in an organization.
Which is why
you should watch him,
and when he's about to cause trouble,
report it to me.
I'll use it to kick him out.
Yes, sir.
Good. I'm counting on you.
I also have a favor to ask.
Yes, what is it?
Once Jin Isoo leaves,
I'd like to pick his replacement.
Sure, you do that.
Yes, sir.
Detective Jin.
Got something to say?
[in English] Nope.
[in Korean] We can finish
the report tomorrow.
Let's go out for drinks tonight.
Okay.
Then I know this celebrity chef...
Let's go somewhere local, in one hour.
Yes, ma'am.
[muttering] She's the worst.
Seriously, the worst.
The absolute worst.
[♪ soft pop music playing in background]
Okay, let's make a toast.
[whispers] Bro.
-Here's to working together.
-Welcome to the team!
-Welcome.
-[Junyoung] Welcome.
[Hyera exhales]
Chief Park?
He was my immediate supervisor.
Wow! What was he like?
[exhales] He was scary.
I learned a lot from him.
We heard so much about you.
-Like how you caught Kim Dusik.
-Kim Dusik?
[Junyoung] Yeah, a serial robber
and killer.
I heard you spent a week on stakeout.
[scoffs] People still talk about that?
Of course.
A whole week? Where?
The convenience store
in front of his girlfriend's house.
I worked there.
I caught him
when he came to buy cigarettes at dawn.
[exclaims]
But...
[spluttering] ...why did you come back?
That's...
No comment.
[muttering] "No comment," my foot.
[grunts]
-Bro, where are you going?
-[Isoo] The restroom.
Then, tell us about the chief.
The chief?
What kind of stuff?
Something cool, or something dirty?
Something dirty.
[all chuckling]
It was summer, around five years ago.
It was a scorching hot day.
It turns out that bastard
was hiding in a pigsty.
The chief just dove right in.
-[chuckles]
-[Junyoung] No way.
The chief?
The stench was unbearable,
but we couldn't say a word.
His wife told him at the door
to strip down and throw it all away.
[all laughing]
I didn't expect that from him.
We didn't order these.
Ah. Over there.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
[Kyungjin] No way!
SCORE OVER 1,000
FOR 4 FREE BEERS
Isoo scored over 1,000 points.
[sighs] This isn't something
just anyone can do.
"Just anyone?"
You haven't seen the champion's photo yet?
Champion?
DART CHAMPION
-Ooh.
-That's amazing.
[scoffs] Champion?
I'm taking that champion's place today.
-Ooh.
-Oh!
-[Kyungjin] Great shot!
-[clapping]
Talk is cheap.
[Kyungjin chuckles] So cool.
[exhales]
Please could you stop them?
We're sorry.
[♪ quirky music playing]
You stepped on the line.
[Hyera] Okay, fine.
I thought he said they don't get along.
They get along really well.
-[grunts sharply]
-[exclaims in annoyance]
Oh!
Detective Joo won.
No wonder she's the dart champion.
Now, let's go.
-Come on.
-[Kyungjin] Great shot!
-Bro.
-Let's go.
[Isoo] I'm not going anywhere.
Oh!
The machine was so shocked, it broke.
[exclaims in dismay]
Let's go. Come on.
Bro.
Learn to accept defeat.
[Kyungjin] Come on.
Let's go.
[Isoo] Huh?
Ah, I'm a really great shot, too.
As great as me?
[scoffs]
[♪ dramatic music playing]
[groans]
[sighs in exasperation]
Learn to accept the results.
That's a tiny kitten.
[laughs smugly]
[game announcer speaking in English]
-[game characters grunting]
-[frantic button-clicking]
[exclaims]
[game announcer reads]
[Junyoung and Kyungjin clapping]
[game characters grunting]
[frantic button-clicking]
-[game announcer reads]
-[exclaims]
[in Korean] Just one more round.
One round.
[snoring]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
Mmm.
[grunts groggily]
[Junyoung] Morning.
Goodness, look at you.
[sighs heavily]
What time did you go home?
[sighs] Around 3:00 a.m.
Detective Joo must be really tired, too.
[groans]
[footsteps approaching]
[in English] Good morning.
[in Korean] Ma'am, are you all right?
[Hyera] Mmm? What do you mean?
Let's finish that report today.
-Yes, ma'am.
-Understood.
[sighs softly]
SEOUL GANGHA POLICE STATION
[keyboard clacking]
AHIN
[mouse clicks]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
AHIN
THERE'S A GHOST IN THE ABANDONED HOUSE!
"Whatever it is, I'll take care of it."
You startled me.
DETECTIVE JIN RESPONDING!
You think you're Batman?
Light a signal, why don't you?
[inhales]
Oh, I do give off that Batman vibe.
[scoffs] That's narcissism.
It's a disorder, you know.
[sighs] You probably don't know,
but I'm the cheat code for solving cases.
[sighs] You should really see me
out there in the field.
I believe I did.
Frozen, after touching the bomb.
What's the report about?
[Ahin] There's a ghost
in the abandoned house.
My name is Park Ahin. I'm a middle school
student from Gangha 3-dong.
My dream is to become
a great police officer.
That's why I have a habit of keeping
an eye out for anything suspicious.
But a few days ago,
I saw these eerie lights floating inside
the abandoned house across the street.
There was a murder there,
so the house hasn't sold in years.
[♪ eerie music plays]
[eerie laughter]
I'm sure it's some kind of vengeful ghost.
It's asking us to catch the killer.
How will you take care of this?
I'll check it out first.
Mmm. To arrest a ghost?
Or perform an exorcism?
What if there's actually
something there, huh?
You can't just brush off a tip, damn it.
By the way,
you're straight-up talking down to me now.
I mean, well,
we're the same rank now,
and the same age.
And you're not my instructor anymore.
Do what you want.
Who am I to stop a nutjob?
-Let's head over there.
-What?
Let's go check it out.
[♪ upbeat music playing]
Aren't you clocking out?
I've got nothing to do at home.
Forget it. I'm going alone.
I should come with you.
What if a ghost latches onto you?
[chuckles] Come on.
[♪ quirky music playing]
Let's take your car.
Why? What is it this time?
Then we can take my bike
and you hang on to my waist.
No, we can just go separately.
Come on, don't be so heartless.
I want to ride in a car like this, too.
Open the door.
[sighs]
[car alarm chirping]
[clicks tongue]
Ooh.
Nice car.
Off we go.
[engine starts]
[tires screech]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
FOR SALE
[gate creaking]
[Isoo shudders]
It's eerie.
Is this a haunted house or something?
[Ahin gasps] Oh, my God.
They actually came.
[Ahin's mother] Ahin, come out for dinner.
I'm not eating.
[Isoo exhales softly]
[Hyera] The body was here.
Do you know what kind of case it was?
No.
-[muffled clattering]
-[glass shattering]
-[muffled screaming]
-[Hyera] There was a struggle,
and they resisted until the end,
but were eventually killed
and became ghosts?
You believe that?
-Ghosts and stuff?
-No.
I would if I saw one, but I never have.
I like horror movies, though. You?
I don't watch that stuff.
[chuckles softly]
So you get scared easily.
Of course not.
I just find them boring, that's all.
Why bother watching that?
[yelps]
-[chuckles]
-Oh, come on!
Really boring, isn't it?
-[chuckles]
-[exhales deeply]
[exhales]
You check upstairs.
I'll check this side.
[sighs]
[muttering] She's seriously annoying.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[exhales deeply]
Oh!
[door creaking]
[animal squeaking]
[yelps]
[exhales sharply]
[♪ ominous music swells, fades]
[blunt thud]
[panting]
[door creaking]
Meow.
[♪ ominous music swells, fades]
-[blunt thud]
-[heavy fall]
[♪ tense, pulsating music playing]
-[Ahin's mother] Park Ahin.
-[Ahin] I said I'm not eating.
Don't you dare make noodles
at midnight again.
Okay, fine. I'm busy.
-What on earth are you watching with--
-Please just...
Good luck making it to the academy.
Just get out.
-[Ahin's mother] Goodness, what are you...
-[door opens]
Park Ahin!
[Hyera coughing]
[♪ tense music playing]
[groaning]
[panting]
[grunts]
Detective Jin.
Jin Isoo!
Nutjob!
Yes, ma'am!
[Hyera grunts]
-What's this?
-Jin Isoo.
Snap out of it.
I'm completely awake.
What's going on?
-Hey, what happened?
-I don't know.
I got attacked out of nowhere.
-[panting]
-[Isoo grunts]
[groans]
[grunts]
[panting] Hey, try to untie this.
[in English] Okay.
[in Korean] I actually have
pretty long fingers.
[grunts]
I got it.
-That's my finger.
-Oh.
Thought it was a rope.
Stop messing around. We could die here.
No one's going to die.
Why are you being so dramatic?
We don't know who attacked us.
Okay, fine.
Just stay still, will you?
[grunts, exhales]
[gasps]
What is it?
Nothing. It's nothing.
No need to be alarmed. Stay calm.
-Stay calm.
-[screams]
Why is this being so difficult?
[grunting]
[sniffs]
Hey, I smell something burning.
She's got a good nose.
[exhales] Is there a fire?
Kind of. No, it's fine.
We're okay for now.
[grunts]
Hey, Jin Isoo.
I'm working on it! Jeez.
Do you see that broken glass over there?
Yeah.
On three, fall left.
Left? Okay.
One, two,
three.
[both groan]
[breathing heavily]
It was my right.
-[breathing heavily]
-You need to be more specific.
Again. One...
-Two, three!
[both groaning, grunting]
[Hyera] Get up.
-Get up.
-One, two, three.
[grunts]
Again. One, two, three.
[both grunting]
-Where is it?
-Go up.
A bit farther.
[both grunting]
Got it.
Be careful.
Don't move. You'll get hurt.
[mutters]
[Hyera grunting]
[♪ ominous music plays]
Fire. [breath trembles]
It's a fire. [breathing heavily]
[landline ringing]
Yes, this is Violent Crime Team 1.
There's a fire.
The detectives went inside,
but now it's on fire.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
[Isoo grunting]
[grunts]
[both panting]
[Isoo groaning]
[grunting]
-[rope snaps]
-[grunts]
[sighs in relief]
[grunting]
-[rope snaps]
-[exhales]
[both panting]
How do we get out?
[rattling]
Like this.
Get out of the way.
[glass shattering]
[clanging]
[in English] Ladies first.
[exhales heavily]
[both coughing]
[breathing heavily]
[exclaims]
[in Korean] If it weren't for me,
you would've burned to death
in that house.
It would've been the end.
Detective Joo,
just stay close to me from now on.
The hero never dies that easily.
You want to live?
Then just stick close to me, okay?
Okay.
[sighs] What do we do now?
Do we jump, or not?
-Like this?
-What?
-[Isoo gasps]
-[explosion]
[both groan]
[both panting]
Nutjob, you okay?
Yeah. I seriously almost died.
[grunts, groans]
You should've told me we were jumping.
Look how high that is.
-[groans]
-[exhales heavily]
The hero never dies that easily.
Stay close to me if you want to live.
[scoffs]
[grunts]
[both continue panting]
There really is something here.
[sighs] I have great instincts, huh?
[scoffs]
Oh, you're bleeding.
I'm fine.
Come on.
Give it here.
-Aah!
-You said you were fine.
You're tying it too tight, so it hurts.
It's to stop the bleeding. [clicks tongue]
You shouldn't have gone overboard.
That's my thing.
[Isoo sighs]
-[gate clunks open]
-[Kyungjin] Jin Isoo!
-Bro!
-[Junyoung] There they are again.
Are you okay?
I'm not, but don't make a fuss.
Are you okay, Detective Joo?
Yes.
What happened?
It was arson.
Someone tied us up and set a fire.
[exhales heavily]
[leaves rustling]
[Ahin] Detective!
[panting shakily]
-[whimpers]
-Oh.
[mouthing]
Who is this?
[whimpers] I'm so sorry. I didn't see
anything because I was eating noodles.
Ah, you must be Ahin.
Are you okay?
Huh?
It's nothing. Don't worry about it.
Have we met somewhere before?
[♪ ominous music playing]
[sirens blaring]
-Take a video of the onlookers.
-Yes, ma'am.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[indistinct chatter]
How did you end up here?
We got a report.
What kind of report?
That middle schooler reported that
someone keeps entering an empty house.
We came to check just in case.
Did you see who attacked you?
They came up from behind.
Without knowing who you were?
Yeah.
It's not some punk
squatting in an empty house.
There's something going on here.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What is this?
Guys, come here. Quickly.
Let's open it up.
The padlock is too new
for a long-abandoned house.
Look. Someone tried to pry it open.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
That?
There's definitely something in there.
Some kind of dark secret.
[distant cameras clicking]
I told you, I've got great instincts.
You two know that.
Get a search warrant.
Why would we need a warrant?
We almost died.
That's not enough.
We'll say it was on fire.
We can't.
Kyungjin.
[mutters]
-[Junyoung sighs]
-[mutters]
Hey, come on.
If you open it now, whatever we find
inside will be inadmissible.
You know the drill.
But...
-[crowbar clinks softly]
-By the way,
why do you keep
talking casually to our team leader?
I told her I'd be respectful,
but she kept telling me to relax.
Goodness.
She's super chill.
Honestly.
Don't open it. Don't you dare.
[footsteps receding]
[sighs wearily]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Isoo exhales deeply]
[softly] Ah...
[cell phone vibrating]
Detective Joo, are you okay? Are you hurt?
No, I'm fine, sir.
[sighs in relief]
What happened?
We don't know yet.
I think we need to do
some more digging on this house.
Okay. I've sent the forensics team,
so wrap it up and go home.
Sir.
We found a suspicious basement here.
But it's locked with a padlock.
Can we get a warrant?
We need to know what kind of case this is
to request a warrant.
Why? You think
it has something to do with the fire?
I'm not sure.
In that case,
investigate first,
then get a warrant if you need to.
Yes, sir.
-We'll have to see about the warrant.
-Okay.
The fire started on the first floor,
then appears to have spread up the stairs.
I heard there was
a murder here a long time ago,
but someone's been in and out since then.
Okay. We'll look for any recent traces.
We'll go collect security footage
from the streets nearby.
Okay.
-Let's go.
-Okay.
[distant metal clanging]
[grunts]
-[Hyera] Jin Isoo!
-[Junyoung] Hey!
-What are you doing?
-I told you not to.
[chain rattling]
Hey!
Is it illegal for a homeowner
to break down his own door?
No way.
I bought this house.
-[chuckles softly]
-You bought it?
The realtor's number
was on the front gate.
FOR SALE
[♪ jaunty music playing]
The owner asked them
to sell it no matter what.
[scoffs] So you just bought it?
[Kyungjin] Wow, bro.
[clapping]
Who just spends money like that...
except you, of course.
You know how to flex.
Mmm.
[sighs] So this is your cheat code.
This is nothing to be surprised about.
You're pretty timid.
Where did you get that hammer?
I borrowed it from Ahin.
They're repairing their wall.
-All right, then.
-[chain rattling]
Now, don't be shy.
-[chain clatters]
-[in English] Welcome.
[door creaking]
[♪ eerie music playing]
[Kyungjin coughing]
[Kyungjin clears throat]
[in Korean] Detective Joo.
That looks newly covered.
[hollow thudding]
Kyungjin.
Stand back.
[sharp clang]
Detective Joo.
[scraping]
[stones clattering]
[exhales deeply]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[Junyoung grunting]
[exclaims]
[Isoo coughs, gags]
GANGHA 3-DONG
BURIED BODIES CASE
[exhales]
How did you end up going to that house?
[Isoo] We received a tip.
What kind of tip?
Someone reported that there was a ghost.
To me.
[♪ jaunty music playing]
Hey, what is he talking about?
Did he just say a ghost?
[chuckles softly] It was a report
of lights in an empty house.
We went to check if it was being used
for criminal activity.
Okay, fine.
Why did you open the basement?
I said wait.
I went ahead and bought the house!
I see.
You bought the house.
[chuckles, exhales]
Right, so,
you uncovered five bodies?
Yes, they're performing the autopsy now.
ONE BODY, BURIED RECENTLY
Four of them are skeletal remains,
so identifying them will take a while.
[Changun sighs]
For now,
Team 1 and 2 will both be on this case.
Make sure this doesn't leak to the press,
and identify the victims quickly. Got it?
-Yes, sir.
-[all] Yes, sir.
[inhales deeply, exhales]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
[examiner] Let's begin the autopsy.
[camera shutter clicking]
I investigated the murder
that happened inside the house.
Around 1:00 a.m. on October 25, 2016,
a couple and their son, a college student,
were all murdered.
There were no signs of forced entry,
but cash and jewelry were gone,
so it was suspected to be
a robbery-homicide,
but the culprit was never caught.
It's a cold case.
No fingerprints, no hair.
Not a single trace was left behind.
So the house was abandoned after that,
and then it was used as a burial site.
By the serial killer.
[Byungsik sighs]
Detective Joo.
The most recently deceased victim
had these glasses in their pants.
[Byungsik] I'll go check it out.
Okay. We'll go after the arsonist.
Got it. Let's go.
-Yes, sir.
-Let's check the footage from the scene.
-Okay.
[mouse clicks]
[♪ gripping music playing]
-[in English] Stop.
-[keyboard key clacks]
[in Korean] That's the guy.
The black hoodie.
-Track him.
-Okay.
[keyboard clacking]
It's a rental.
-Run the plate.
-Got it.
Excuse me.
We're with the police.
How can I help you?
Could you tell us
where you supplied these glasses?
I'll check right away.
DOHYUN CAR RENTAL
[♪ gripping music continues]
Who rented this car?
[agent] Oh, that car
hasn't been returned yet.
One moment, please.
Oh...
It's that car there.
Right.
[door chimes]
Hey, hey.
Police.
-[knocks window]
-Please come out, serial killer.
Careful. He could be armed.
You're right.
[knocks window]
Come out.
Or we'll break it.
[window whirring]
JEONG DAEUN
GANGHA 3-DONG ARSON SUSPECT
[Isoo breathes sharply]
[inhales sharply]
Inside that abandoned house,
did you attack us?
What?
Did you knock us out and tie us up?
No, how would I even do that?
Last night, you were
at the abandoned house
at 14-1 Gangha 3-dong, right?
Yes.
I started the fire.
[exhales in disbelief]
We almost burned to death.
My team leader hurt her arm.
I'm really sorry.
I didn't know there were people inside.
Why did you start the fire?
Because Hyeonsu disappeared,
and no one will believe me.
Please start from the beginning.
Hyeonsu is a lawyer.
[♪ soft suspenseful music playing]
We've been dating for three years,
and we were about to get married.
[vocalizing the "Bridal Chorus"]
4 MONTHS AGO
[both chuckle]
JEONG DAEUN'S FIANCÉ
PARK HYEONSU
[both vocalizing the "Bridal Chorus"]
-[exclaims] It's raining.
-Hold on.
-What?
-It's raining so suddenly.
-[both giggle]
-[Hyeonsu] Let's go.
[♪ melancholy music playing]
[Daeun] He was a really kind person.
When we were busy planning our wedding,
he said something important had come up.
His former classmate was in trouble
and needed his help.
Not long after, she was murdered.
But then I was told
that Hyeonsu was the killer.
I kept saying
he'd never do something like that,
but no one would believe me.
They said all the evidence was there,
that she and Hyeonsu used to date,
that he stalked her to get back with her,
then killed her.
But that doesn't make any sense.
Sir.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What is it?
PARK HYEONSU
[exhales softly]
Then why did you go to that house?
Hyeonsu installed
a location-sharing app on my phone.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
This app will show you where I am.
[chuckles]
[gasps softly]
We can't see each other very often.
Now, if you just check the app,
you'll know where I'm working.
Oh, you.
[both chuckle]
[Daeun] On the day of the murder,
Hyeonsu's last location was that house.
At first, I was too shaken
and forgot all about the app.
When I later checked
and went to his last location,
it was an abandoned house.
Hyeonsu has no connection
to that neighborhood.
Wait, so,
you went in there alone?
Weren't you scared?
I asked the police to investigate,
but the detective in charge
wouldn't listen.
[♪ gripping music playing]
But there was a strange basement there.
I tried to open it...
...but I couldn't.
So I set the place on fire,
thinking they might find something
while putting it out.
I honestly didn't know someone was inside.
By any chance,
did you see anyone suspicious there?
No, no one.
[sighs softly]
[pen clicks]
[sighs heavily]
[door opens]
[Junyoung] Jiwon.
[door closes]
[Dr. Yoon] Hi.
Have you eaten at all?
No. [exhales]
I wasn't really hungry.
I got you a sandwich.
Thanks.
I'll eat it later.
[sighs]
Did you find anything?
[exhales heavily]
We start work on the skeletal remains
tomorrow morning.
We performed the autopsy
on the most recent victim first...
[inhales deeply]
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
...but the body's too decomposed
to recover any fingerprints.
Look here. There are three stab wounds.
And the wrists have marks
that appear to be from duct tape.
So the victim was stabbed while tied up?
[sighs heavily]
Yes.
DETECTIVE DIVISION
You? Against me?
That's ridiculous.
It's him.
The detective who wouldn't believe me.
Sir, how did this happen?
We didn't make a mistake.
INVESTIGATION REPORT
Three months ago, in Yuseon-dong,
Kim Minseo was murdered.
[♪ foreboding music playing]
-Hello.
-[muffled screaming]
-[flesh squelching]
[groans softly]
[knife clatters]
[Byungsik] The suspect fled
on a motorcycle,
entered Park Hyeonsu's house...
[suspect grunting]
...then drove away in his car.
[inhales deeply]
Even so,
would a man about to get married,
who was sharing his location
with his girlfriend,
plan and execute a murder?
It doesn't make sense.
[♪ suspenseful music playing]
What was his motive?
Park Hyeonsu kept texting her,
asking to meet up.
[Hyeonsu] Did you take care of it?
I'll be waiting,
so tell me when you're done.
If you keep this up, I'm not holding back.
Please meet me just once.
You want to see me lose it?
Kim Minseo kept refusing.
Kim Minseo
had filed a stalking complaint before.
Park Hyeonsu's fingerprints were
on a knife found at the scene.
That knife was the knife
missing from Park Hyeonsu's house.
We also found the disguise
he used as a courier inside his house.
We confirmed the weapon,
fingerprints, motive, and movements.
Then he suddenly disappeared,
so we put him on the wanted list.
But...
these belong to Park Hyeonsu.
Got the autopsy results?
They'll do the rest tomorrow,
so this is just the most recent victim's.
A male in his 30s. Died three months ago,
and stabbed to death while bound.
[♪ tense music playing]
Wait, so,
the murder suspect you were after
three months ago
was murdered and his body was found
at the abandoned house?
[Isoo inhales deeply]
Did someone get revenge on him?
Does Kim Minseo have any family?
Her husband and her parents.
How can you find and kill someone
even the police couldn't find?
What about the abandoned house?
Did he even go there?
His phone went offline near there
and never came back online.
His car was found
abandoned at Incheon Port.
We assumed
he'd snuck out of the country by sea,
so we had Interpol issue a Red Notice.
[exhales deeply]
Let's verify this first.
Ask them to compare
the body's DNA with Park Hyeonsu's.
Yes, ma'am.
[cell phone vibrating]
Yes, sir.
Yes, understood.
[exhales deeply]
[knock at door]
Yes, come in.
Detective Joo, have a seat.
[door closes]
I'm going fishing at dawn.
[chuckles softly]
If I catch some big ones,
would you like one?
They don't call me
the Sea King's eldest son for nothing.
I'm all right, thank you.
So,
I hear Jin Isoo bought a house.
Yes, sir.
And you found five bodies inside?
-Yes, sir.
-[gasps]
Does he just make trouble
wherever he goes?
-Is there nothing wrong with that?
-Pardon?
I mean, is there anything
we can find fault with?
Can a police officer
just buy up a house like that?
There's no reason he can't.
He's not breaking the law.
We found five bodies there
and prevented it
from becoming the perfect crime,
so it's a good thing.
How is that a good thing?
Come on,
I just want to make it to retirement
in peace, for God's sake.
Should we hand this over
to Seoul Headquarters?
It's a big case.
Don't worry, sir.
We'll catch whoever's behind this.
[♪ gripping music playing]
NO USABLE FINGERPRINTS
SUSPECT, VICTIM
PARK HYEONSU, AGE 34
KIM MINSEO, AGE 34
VICTIM KIM MINSEO'S HOUSE
SUSPECT PARK HYEONSU'S HOUSE
Ma'am, we got a match on the DNA.
It is Park Hyeonsu.
AUTOPSY REPORT
Who could have killed Park Hyeonsu?
Don't just think about him.
There are five bodies
killed by the same guy.
Then, was Park Hyeonsu
murdered by a serial killer?
No, wait.
Let's start over.
What if Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one
who killed Kim Minseo?
You're saying they're professionals?
Yes.
If Park Hyeonsu wasn't the one
who killed Kim Minseo...
It's the perfect crime.
Right? Here, look.
Look. The target.
A victim to frame as the suspect.
If they kill the target and the suspect,
then make him go missing,
the case cannot be solved.
[Hyera] Five perfect crimes.
You need at least two people
to make this possible.
They're methodical and cold.
Park Hyeonsu would've been first,
since they sent those texts.
[Hyera] First, they overpowered
Park Hyeonsu.
One of them would've kept watch.
They sent the harassing messages.
-Hello.
-Hello, delivery.
Then, after killing the target...
-[muffled screaming]
-[flesh squelching]
[Hyera] ...they dressed up
as Park Hyeonsu.
[door beeps]
[muffled] Help me!
-[grunting]
-[flesh squelching]
Then they buried him and disappeared.
So they're professional killers?
Yes.
They must've been hired to do it.
[♪ ominous music playing]
Those bastards completely fooled me.
We need to start this case over.
The ones who attacked
you and Isoo must be the real culprits.
If they came to the house...
It means they killed someone else.
They were there to bury the body.
[suspect] Wait.
It's blood. [exclaims]
KILLER 1
JANG JAECHUN
It leaked.
KILLER 2
JO BEOMKI
What do we do?
[♪ tense music playing]
This is bad.
Taegwang.
FLEX X COP 2
EPISODE 3
THE KILLER OF KILLERS
YU TAEGWANG
[♪ upbeat pop music playing,
Hersh "Shadows In The Night"]
Special Cast.
Lee Hakju, Park Soi
[Taegwang] We got a new job.
Where are you?
-[Kyungjin] I got their location.
-[tires screech]
I need the chopper.
This is straight out of a soap opera.
You're Korean, right?
-I don't know.
-You don't know?
-Freeze.
-We're flying out at dawn.
[Hyera] They're ruthless killers,
so civilians could get hurt.
Beomki!
[Hyera] If we want to catch them...
Let's hire them to kill someone.
Is this how you normally investigate?
I won't let you down.
You were a real scumbag.
[Taegwang] We all go down together.
[Junyoung] So the perp's still here.
[gunshot]
Jin Isoo!
[♪ captivating music playing]
[Taegyun] Who is that?
Did we arrest a gang boss?
Is that Park?
[♪ quirky music playing]
Gosh.
What are they doing?
-[car door closes]
-I have no idea, sir.
Our district
is just strange overall.
Translated by Hyesoo Lee